[{"question": " it's so weird, how did joey end up kissing charlie last night? i thought you'd end up kissing charlie.", "answer": " hey, i thought i'd end up kissing charlie too ok? but surprise!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i missed most of the party  charlie's a girl, right?", "answer": " yes, she is this new professor of my department that i did not kiss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " i don't know why joey had to kiss her! i mean, of all the girls at the party, god!", "answer": " why do you care so much?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yes rachel, why do you care so much?", "answer": "  be-cause ross is the father of my child! you know... and i... want him to hook up with lots of women!  i just... all i'm saying is... i don't think that joey and charlie have anything in common.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh, i don't know, they seem to have a shared interest in each other's tonsils...", "answer": " wow, joey and a professor! can you imagine if they had kids and if the kids got her intelligence and joey's raw sexual magnetism... oh, those nerds will get laaaaaid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " all right, so... ross, you're ok with all this? i mean...", "answer": " yeah, it's no big deal. i mean, i just met her and i'm fine with it...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh, god. i forgot how hot she was!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " i'm gonna get some more coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh, you know what? i'll come with you!", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  so, a professor, uh?", "answer": " yeah! she is cool, and she's so smart! her mind is totally acrimonious .  that's not how she used it...?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  i feel like i owe you an explanation. i don't ordinarily go around kissing guys at parties. i'm... well, i'm kind of embarrassed. i really hope you don't think less of me.", "answer": " uhm no! think less of you! no, i don't think less of you. i mean, you saw someone you liked and you kissed them. i mean, those people who like someone and don't kiss them... those-those people are stupid, i hate those people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " you know, actually i'm a little surprised to myself. i mean, joey is so different from the guys i usually date. i mean, they're all professors, and intellectuals, and paleontologists mostly, you know, very cerebral...", "answer": " yeah, i know the type.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh, oh! wow, i love those! where did you get them?", "answer": " i bought them off ebay! they used to belong to the late shania twain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  phoebe, shania twain is still alive!", "answer": " oh... then i overpaid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey, what's this?", "answer": " oh, it's a gift certificate to this new spa in soho.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh, you can't show phoebe this! she hates those corporate massage chains.", "answer": " ah, why, now i can't get a massage? there are so many things that she disapproves of! i can't eat veal, i can't wear fur, i can't go hunting...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " do you wanna go hunting?", "answer": " well, i would like to have the option!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  what's up?  hey, rachel!!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " no, you can't go there! you know how i feel about these \"big massage places\"! they're putting people like me out of business!", "answer": " and she wants to go hunting, too!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " phoebe, come on, i don't wanna waste it! it would be like throwing away a hundred bucks!", "answer": " ok, this is not about the money, ok? it's about... it's about corporate greed destroying our hearts and leaving us... the hollow shells.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i don't care about any of that!!", "answer": " well, do you care about friendship?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " i feel really strongly about this, rachel. please, don't use this gift certificate. i'm asking you as a friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh, not as a friend, phoebe!! fine, i won't use it!", "answer": " promise?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " i promise.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  hey honey! i missed you today!", "answer": " oh, yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah.  what d'you wanna do tonight?", "answer": " oh, well... maybe we could...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " ok, trying to turn me on by making a mess? know your audience! besides, tomorrow we're doing those fertility tests and until then you need to keep your tadpoles in the tank.", "answer": " we really need to take those tests?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " honey, we've been trying to have a baby for over a year. i think it's a good idea to find out if everything's ok. just a few routine tests.", "answer": " but i don't wanna do it in a cup!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what is the big deal?", "answer": " it's weird! in a doctor's office?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " it's not ok to do it in a doctor's office but it is ok to do it in a parked car behind a taco bell?", "answer": "  i cannot believe ross told you that!  and in my defense, it was a wendy's!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " look, i don't wanna do this test either, but i really do think it's a good idea!", "answer": " yeah, ok. i'm sure that doctor's office can't be worst than on a class trip to the hershey's factory!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  oh!", "answer": " oh, yeah! rachel talks too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " heeey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " come on in, how are ya?", "answer": " i'm good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " can i offer you a drink?", "answer": " please, i've been crazed all day! i had a meeting with the dean, and my syllabus for summer school is due and i'm writing the foreword for a friend's book...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " uh-oh. i hade a pretty hectic day at work too, today i had to open a door and go  ohhhh!", "answer": " so i am just so excited to be here. and i can't wait to start exploring the city!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, you mean it? that would be so fun!", "answer": " yeah, definitely, definitely. ok, what do you wanna see first?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh, well, we can go see the chronos quartet at the avery fisher hall.", "answer": "  ok!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " and there is a collection of walt whitman letters on display at the public library.", "answer": " i know, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " and first, i have to see the met!", "answer": " ok, let me stop you right there. the mets suck, ok? you wanna see the yankees.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " no, no, no, not the mets, the met, singular!", "answer": " which one, they all suck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " the museum!", "answer": "  i don't think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  hi there!", "answer": "  hello, welcome to lavender day spa spa. how may i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " oh, hi. i have a massage appointment under rachel green, and here is my gift certificate.", "answer": " this has been torn up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " and... taped back together.", "answer": " ok well, i'll call you as soon as your massage therapist is ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " ok", "answer": " have a seat through the glass doors.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  through the glass doors.", "answer": " through the glass doors.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " phoebe, your next client's in the waiting room.", "answer": " ok. do we have to talk like that then they're not around?  oh, no, no! listen, is there someone who can fill in for me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " sorry, everyone is booked!", "answer": " but that woman can't know i work here. she's a friend of mine and i made this big stink about how awful this massage chains are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " then why you work here?", "answer": " 'cause it's good money! but that doesn't change the fact that this is an evil blood sucking corporate machine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " well, i think this is a great place to work!", "answer": "  ok, are they listening?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i need to talk to you about charlie.", "answer": "  oh, do you, do you really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " yeah, i'm... i'm kind of having a little problem.", "answer": " look, if you don't know what the word \"acrimonious\" means, just don't use it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " no, look, you know charlie, right? she's cool, she's funny, her body is soo...", "answer": " get to the problem!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yes. it's just that she's so much smarter than all the girls i've ever dated! combined! i don't want her to think i'm stupid!", "answer": "  are you wearing two belts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  eh, what do you know!", "answer": " you were saying you didn't want to seem stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " right, right, right, well, she wants to go to all this cultural places and i don't know how to talk about that stuff. you gotta help me out!", "answer": " you know, i really don't want to get involved in you guy's relationship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " please, c'mon, you're the smartest person i know and i really like this girl, ok, i don't wanna lose her.", "answer": "  fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " ok. let's see. oh, you should take her to the met!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " the metsss!", "answer": " oh, no! the met! the metropolitan museum of art.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  oh, that's what she meant!  you know, if they're gonna shorten it, they should call it the muse! you know, short for museum, and avoid all the confusion!", "answer": " yeah, most of it it's a place packed with confused angry baseball fans!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " ok, all right, so i'll take her to the met.", "answer": " yeah, uh, uh, ok, there's this great rare bookstore on madison avenue. you know what? she loves architecture, you know what you should do? you should take a walk down fifth to the saint patrick's cathedral and there there's this great little pastry shop that she'd love.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " geez, sounds like you should be going on this date!", "answer": " but i'm not! . you know what if you're in the mood for thai food...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " whoa, whoa, whoa! slow down, you go way too fast. ok? just go back to the met, ok?", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " you got to tell me exactly what to do there.", "answer": " ok, when you walk in the museum, take the right, that's the antiquities wing. ancient egypt, mesopotamia, up to the byzantine empire.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i have a weird feeling about this place.  how do i know that they are not gonna secretly videotape me and put it all over the internet.", "answer": " because, honey, i mean this in the sweetest way possible, nobody is gonna wanna watch that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " mr. bing?  here you are! you'll go into that room and deposit your specimen into the container.", "answer": " deposit my specimen? you know, usually i have to call a 900 number for that kind of talk. thanks, got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey, honey, my test is down the hall, are you sure you're going to be ok?", "answer": " yeah, i guess!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i know this is embarrassing, but nobody cares! no one here even knows you!", "answer": " oh my god!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, come on! commercial break", "answer": " ah ahahahhahaa! how great is this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " hey, we're probably fertile, let's go home!", "answer": " why are you here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " well, sid and i are trying again and we had trouble last time because apparently we...", "answer": "  no no no... i mean, why? why is she here??", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " oh! someone's a little cranky today cuz they have to do it in a cup!  oh! they gave you the kiddy size .", "answer": " what!?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " please... go!  just let me know if you need a hand!", "answer": "  i think it just fell off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  hello \"ja\", it's time for your massage, ja! put your face in the hole.", "answer": " wow, a swedish massage from a real swedish person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " okay, then i'm swedish...", "answer": " so, what's your name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " it's a normal swedish name... ikea...", "answer": " oh... what an interesting name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ja!", "answer": " you know i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  time for your scalp massage!", "answer": "  wow... i really love your...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " is something wrong?", "answer": " no, it's just that uhm... it feels so good... ikea...  yeah, say hey, you'll know this, what's the capital of sweden?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  uhm... stockholm.", "answer": " damn! i wish i knew if that was right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  note the painterly lines and subtle impasto on this canvas. monet painted quickly and usually outdoors as his elusive subject was light itself.", "answer": " now, do you have any idea what you just said?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  no, no, my mouth says the words, my brain is thinking monster trucks!", "answer": " ok now, remember, when you get to the museum, monet is not spelt m-o-n-a-y. i just... i wrote that out phonetically for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah, yeah that means... you know? we just... we don't have time for this.", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " ok, but you know what? i gotta say, i'm really impressed that you were able to memorize all this so quickly!", "answer": " ah! i'm an actor! i can memorize anything! last week on \"days\" i had to say \"frontal temporal zygomatic craniotomy\".", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " wow. what does that mean?", "answer": " no idea! but the guy i said it to dies in the next scene so i guess it means \"you're gonna get eaten by a bear\".", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " ok! so let's move on to the renaissance?", "answer": " ok, caravaggio uses chiaroscuro here to highlight the anguish of the central figure. touch it, it's really bumpy! .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " nah ah! nah ah!  no no no! no ad-libbing and dude, you can't touch the paintings.", "answer": " come on! you...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  my specimen is in the room and i just want to thank whoever knocked on the door while i was in there. really helped speed the process along!  janice! you're not... gone?", "answer": " oh! sid is still in his room. i don't allow porn at home so this is like a vacation for him. so did you do it? did you make your deposit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah! yeah... the hard part is over!", "answer": " that's not the hard part honey! the hard part is what comes next, i mean aren't you worried about the results?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " i haven't... i haven't even thought about the results yet... i just assumed that everything was gonna be ok.", "answer": " oh! well, you know what? it probably is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  yeah, but what if it's not? what if there is a reason why we can't have a baby?", "answer": " oh, chandler, look. you and monica are meant to have children. i am sure it's gonna be just fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  oh, oh, yeah, ok, thanks. i can't believe i didn't even think of that. i guess i was just so worried about having to... come here and do... 'that'...", "answer": " what, you can do it in the parking lot of a taco bell, but you can't do it at a doctor's office?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " wow, ikea... what a rich culture. uhm, you know what? i have a friend who is a masseuse.", "answer": " oh, ja! ja!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " uhu, uhu... and why do you think that is?", "answer": " i don't know... maybe it's because she has got such callousy fingers from playing crummy guitar...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " or... maybe she has trouble loosening your knots because you're such a high maintenance tight ass!", "answer": "  phoebe!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you know it's me?", "answer": " for like a half an hour! man, you can lie about sweden!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " how can you come here?", "answer": " how could you not tell me you worked here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i don't have to tell you everything!", "answer": " yes you do, if you're going to make me feel guilty for getting a free massage!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " tips not included.", "answer": " oh! phoebe, why did you lie to me about working here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " because i was ashamed ok? i sold out for the cash! and then they give me benefits like medical, and dental, and a 401k. but you know... you pay a price. now i'm this corporate stooge and punching a clock and ugh! paying taxes!", "answer": " phoebe, honey, if you hate it so much, you should walk out there right now and quit! be true to what you believe in! honey, you have principles and i so admire that! i don't have any!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " you know what? you are right. i am gonna quit. it's time i took my life back!", "answer": " good for you pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " ok.", "answer": " okay  if you guys have microphones in there too, i didn't mean any of that. i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  respectfully, professor r. geller.  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " hey, how was the met?", "answer": " the museum was amazing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " yeah? joey really knows his art, huh?", "answer": " not so much, no. he had clearly memorized all the stuff to say, and some of it didn't even make any sense.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " what do you mean?", "answer": " well, for one, he was talking about paintings that were nowhere around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  wait a minute... when you guys walked into the met, did you go to the right?", "answer": " no, we went to the left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  oh joey, joey! but still, i mean, it seems like you guys are having a great time together.", "answer": " yeah, it's fun .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " actually, you know, joey is your friend, and you don't really know me that well; it would be weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " what, i mean, a little, but no, what, go on.", "answer": " well... i'm just thinking that maybe he's not the right guy to be with right now, maybe i should be with someone... i have more in common with. you know what i mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  yeah. but you know what? i think you should give joey a chance. i mean, he's a great guy, and sure he doesn't know that much about art but you know, you can always talk about that with someone else.", "answer": " yeah, i guess that's true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " and if you think about it, i mean the reason he memorized all that stuff is because he thought it was important to you. you know, that's the kind of guy joey is.", "answer": " he is very sweet. plus he's hot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  you're ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " yeah, let's go.   thanks ross.", "answer": "  hey ross! that art stuff worked, you hooked me up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " glad i could help man.", "answer": " although some of that stuff wasn't where you said it was gonna be, but...  i made it work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " hey sweetie.", "answer": " doctor connelly just called.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " with good news?  of course it is not good news, you just said  \"doctor connelly just called\". if it was good news you would have said  \"doctor connelly just called! \" but so what is it? is there a problem, uh? is there a problem with me or with you?", "answer": " actually it's both of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " apparently my sperm have low motility and you have an inhospitable environment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " oh... what does that mean?", "answer": " it means that my guys won't get off their barcaloungers and you have a uterus that is prepared to kill the ones that do.  it means...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": "  it means that we can keep trying, but there's a good chance this may never happen for us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": "  oh my god!", "answer": " i'm sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " well, we're gonna... we're gonna figure this out.", "answer": "  i know. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " good morning phoebe.", "answer": "  good morning receptionist.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " here's your schedule for the day. your first client is in room no. 1.", "answer": " rachel green?  son of a bitch, she came back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s9/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}]